designimo.com 2019-03-18

# Privacy Policy

### OVERVIEW

This privacy policy describes how Designimo.com maintains, uses and shares information that we may collect when you use our website. 

We may change this privacy policy from time to time. Any such changes will be posted here. If we make a material change in the way we use your personal information, we will prominently note the change on the Sites and/or email you regarding the change at least thirty (30) days prior to the change taking effect.

We do not collect, use, or disclose any information about users of our Sites except as described in this Privacy Policy. 

### HOW WE COLLECT AND USE INFORMATION

Some of the information we collect when you use any of the Sites, such as your name, company name, postal address, email address, credit card information or telephone numbers, may allow you to be identified ("Personal Information").

Registration: If you would like to create, edit or purchase rights to use a logo or other design ("Design"), order any merchandise displaying a Design ("Merchandise") or use any other products or services that we may offer from time to time, you will be asked to provide Personal Information, which we will use to fulfill your request. 

Marketing Partnerships: We may make your Personal Information available to other organizations to market products or services that may be of interest to you. Such marketing may be via email, telephone, direct mail or other means. By providing your Personal Information on any of the Sites, you are expressly consenting to receive such marketing communications from us and others. 

Inquiries. If you send us a comment or question or make an inquiry to customer support, we will retain the information that you provide to us for the purpose of responding to you, as well as for improving the Sites and our customers' use of our services.

Visitors: If you are just visiting our website and not creating or editing a Design, ordering Merchandise, registering, requesting information, contacting us, or posting to a public area of any of the Sites, we do not ordinarily collect any Personal Information about you.

Pre-Populating Forms: When you enter certain contact information on websites of our marketing partners and then link to one of the Sites, your URL parameters may capture and transmit to us personal information that you provided on the partner website, such as your name, address, phone number or email address. We then use that information, for your convenience, to pre-populate Designs or forms on the Sites. If you decide not to permit cookies on your computer, this may affect your ability to use the Sites.

Communicating with You. We may use information that we collect from you for the purpose of communicating with you and responding to your inquiries. Those communications could, for example, take the form of service updates, promotions for products or services that we or one of our marketing partners provide, or e-newsletters.

Service Providers: We may at times contract with third party service providers to perform functions for us. These service providers may be given access to the information we collect for the purpose of performing those functions, but they will be contractually bound to maintain the confidentiality of the information and not to use it for any other purpose.

Business Transfers: If we were to transfer all or substantially all of our assets to another company, one of the assets we would likely include in the transfer is our database of Personal Information.

Disclosures for Legal Reasons: We will disclose Personal Information when we are required to do so by law, regulation or securities exchange requirement, for example, in response to a court order or subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement or other governmental agency's request or when we believe such disclosure is appropriate to protect our legal rights or to safeguard anyone's property or safety.

### COLLECTION OF INFORMATION BY THIRD PARTIES

Some of the advertisements you see on the Site are selected and delivered by third parties, such as ad networks, advertising agencies, advertisers, and audience segment providers. These third parties may collect information about you and your online activities, either on the Site or on other websites, through cookies, web beacons, and other technologies in an effort to understand your interests and deliver to you advertisements that are tailored to your interests. Please remember that we do not have access to, or control over, the information these third parties may collect. The information practices of these third parties are not covered by this privacy policy. 

You may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page and you may opt out of certain other third parties' use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page. We may also use Remarketing Dynamic Ads, a feature that uses the Teracent cookie. You may opt out use of the Teracent Cookie by visiting the Teracent opt-out page. In addition, we may use DoubleClick's remarketing pixels, which you may opt out of by visiting either the DoubleClick opt-out page or the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.

We may offer you the opportunity to contact other companies, such as advertisers, marketing affiliates and content providers, to obtain information or to buy products or services. You decide when and whether to give your Personal Information to these companies. If you provide information, its use and security is governed by the policies and practices of those companies and not by this privacy policy.

We make no representations or warranties about any of these other companies or their privacy or security policies. Once you click through to an unaffiliated website, this privacy policy no longer applies. We urge you to read the applicable policies of these other companies and their websites.

### YOUR PRIVACY CHOICES

If you would like us to stop sending you email or otherwise communicating with you; would like us not to disclose your Personal Information to marketing partners or advertisers; or would like to access your registration information to correct or delete it, you may send us a request at legalnotice(at)Designimo.com. We will endeavor to satisfy such requests within a reasonable time. Any marketing emails that we send you will provide an opportunity for you to opt out of receiving further such communications from us. Note that we may not be able to provide you with our services if we delete your information. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the information we collect is reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete and current.

The Website Policies and Terms & Conditions may be changed or updated occasionally to meet the requirements and standards. Therefore the Customers’ are encouraged to frequently visit these sections in order to be updated about the changes on the website. Modifications will be effective on the day they are posted.

### SECURITY

We maintain all Personal Information with physical, electronic, and managerial safeguards to help ensure the security and confidentiality of the data against reasonably foreseeable risks. Security is designed to prevent unauthorized use, access, disclosure, destruction, and changes of data. For example, we restrict access to our computing facilities to individuals identified by management as needing access to perform their jobs. 

All credit/debit cards details and personally identifiable information will NOT be stored, sold, shared, rented or leased to any third parties. 

### CHILDREN

The Sites are intended for use by adults. We do not target, or knowingly collect any Personal Information from, children under the age of 13. 

### ACCOUNTABILITY

We are committed to adhering to our privacy policy and applicable laws and to making your online experience secure and valuable. If you have a question, request, complaint, dispute or concern related to this privacy policy, you may send a message by email to support(at)designimo.com, as applicable.
